luxola.com 2014-12-21

# Privacy Policy - How we store and protect your data - Luxola

This privacy policy explains what personal information is collected through our various online channels, how that information is used, to whom it's disclosed, and how it's safeguarded. Unless indicated otherwise, this policy applies only to personal information collected through the online channel where this policy is displayed or linked by us, such as the Web Site or site (www.luxola.com); our mobile websites and microsites; and Luxola pages on social media sites.

By "personal information" we mean (1) your identifying information (like name, home address, and email address), and also (2) descriptive information (like tastes and preferences) if coupled with your identifying information ("personally identifying information"). We may refer to Luxola as "we," "us," or "our" throughout this privacy policy.

This privacy policy answers these questions: What personal information is collected and how is it used? How is technology used to serve our advertisements on other Web sites and what choices do you have? How does this Web site interact with third-party Web sites and content? What information do we share with partners and third parties (or what information may they access because of the services they provide to us)? What choices do you have over how your information is used? How do you update your personal information? How do we secure your information on our site? Where is personal information stored and processed? Whom should you contact with questions or concerns? When was this policy last updated? What personal information is collected and how is it used?

**What personal information is collected and how is it used?**

  1. Information Collected Directly from You and Others through this Site or online channel We collect personal information directly from you to do all the things typically associated with electronic and mobile commerce Web sites. Examples of the information we collect include name, address, mobile phone number, email address, personal preferences, credit card number, purchase and ordering information, demographical information, and responses to survey questions.

This information is collected at various places on our site: for instance, when you check out with your online order; subscribe to mailers, email offers, and mobile messaging offers; participate in surveys; join LX Insider; enter contests or sweepstakes; or interact with special-event or program offers.

We collect information about you and, if you provide it, we collect information about those you know. For example, we collect your gift recipient's contact information to process your gift orders. We may also collect contact information about your friends and family members when you participate in one of our refer-a-friend programs. In these instances, we may send a message to your friend or family member on your behalf. Please ensure that you only submit email addresses of individuals with whom you have a personal or family relationship and who would want to receive the message from you.

On our social media pages we may collect information about you and, if you allow, about your friends on the social media site, through (1) an application or form accessed through a social media page which links to this privacy policy, and (2) through the Luxola shopping page located on certain Luxola social media pages.

We use this collected information to do things like: • process your online orders; • open an online account at your request; • personalize your online experience with content and offers that are tailored to your interests; • provide customer service, whether it's responding to a request or following up on an order; • include you in surveys and contests; • enable you to post your content, such as comments or images; • facilitate networks of online social activity centered around our products and services; • improve our website, improve the manner in which offers are made on our website, improve purchase decisions of our visitors and the interactions visitors have with our website; • enable you to interact with third-party partners or content service providers, whether by linking to their sites, viewing their content within our Web environment, or by viewing our content within their Web environment; • market our products and services that may be of interest to you (for instance, we may add you to our email or mailing list when you make an online purchase); and • collaborate with partners and other third parties to organise joint marketing and promotional campaigns, offers or contests, which may require disclosure of your information to such third parties.

In addition, customer reviews are available on the Website and may be available on other Luxola online channels where this policy is displayed or linked. These features enable you to post your content, such as comments, product reviews, images, audio and similar content. If your content complies with our rules and terms of use, any portion of it may be published on our Web site(s), and in our stores, emails, online marketing, mobile sites, social media pages, microsites, mailers, and other media. This published content could identify details concerning you.

  1. Information We Observe or Collect through Technology
    
           a. Navigational and Location Information

When you visit this Web site or an online channel where this policy is linked, we collect navigational information, such as browser type and version, service-provider identification, IP address, the site from which you came, and the site to which you navigate. Navigational information is largely anonymous in the sense that it doesn't contain your name, address, phone number, email address or other information that directly identifies you. However, we may associate this navigational information with your personal information if you provide it. When collecting the IP address, we may also be able to determine location information such as city, country, a designated marketing area and the ISP being used. We will also collect the type of mobile device you are using when connecting to our mobile website so we can provide the mobile website version best suited for your device.
    
            b. Cookies and Clear gifs

To better understand what you do while on our site, we use a browser feature known as a cookie. A cookie is a small data file that's stored by your Web browser on your computer or device. It's used to do things like see how you navigate our Web site, and remember you and your online purchases when you return. This helps us improve our site, provide better Customer Care, tailor your online experience, and tailor offers to you based on your unique tastes, location and/or purchase history.

We also use clear-gifs (also known as a Web beacon, pixel tags or Web bug) on our Web site, mobile site, microsites, and social media pages and in our emails. A clear gif is a nearly invisible pixel-sized graphic image on a Web page, Web-based document or email message. It helps us do things like view the URL of the page on which the clear gif appears and the time our Web site or email in question is viewed. Clear gifs in emails help us confirm the receipt of, and response to, our emails, including those that you forward to friends and family; and they help deliver a more personalized online experience. Overall, these technologies may be used to help us see which of our interactive experiences online users like most: for example, by keeping track of the number of times a video, widget or other media is accessed or embedded on social networking sites; and on which social networking sites it is embedded, based on inquiries that are sent to our Web site.

Cookies and clear gifs also allow us to associate your online navigational or transactional information with any personal information you provide or we otherwise collect (such as name, address, phone number, email address, and IP address). We'll associate this information to deliver products and services to you; to improve our business; to transact business; and to market our products and services to you on this and other Web sites and through a variety of media like email, mobile advertising, and direct mail. As an example, we may use cookies to keep track of what you put into your shopping bag. That can help us contact you if your online session is disrupted in mid-purchase, resulting in an abandoned cart. We can also use this technology to determine whether you'd be interested in participating in special events, given your preferences. The end-result is a more personalized experience that's tailored to your needs and tastes.

     3. Information Others Observe or Collect through Technology

We evaluate and select third-party service providers to help us provide certain features on this site and analyze our visitors' site and purchase preferences. The following provides more information about these service providers. We use analytics companies to better understand your use of this Web site, and Web capabilities like embeddable widgets. For instance, these third parties may serve surveys to determine satisfaction with the Web site and then tie the responses to actual behavior on the Web site. We also use third parties so that we can evaluate and understand your online and store purchases to provide tailored offers and information to you. This information also allows us to improve this Web site, and Web capabilities. They accomplish this by using some or all of the technologies described in Information We Observe or Collect Through Technology.

**How is technology used to serve our advertisements on other Web sites and what choices do you have?**

We contract with third-party advertising companies to deliver tailored online display and banner advertising to you on other Web sites. To serve this advertising, these third party companies place, use, or rely on technology, such as cookies and clear gifs, as customers interact with us through our Web sites and interact with other Web sites. Once this information is gathered, it helps us select tailored ads for placement on these other Web sites, based upon a customer's shopping history and experience with us. These companies also provide information to us, which we, in turn, use to gauge how effective our ads are. For information about opt out programs that these third party advertising companies participate in, and the effect of opting out, click the following: [NAI Opt Out] (http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) and [DAA Opt Out] 9http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) (you'll then leave this site for centrally managed online sites where you may specify your preferences under those programs). You can also click the preference icon that may appear on some of our advertising served through use of these technologies. You should also note that our systems may not recognize "Do Not Track" headers from some or all browsers.

**How does this Web site interact with third-party Web sites and content?**

We may enable you to navigate to third-party sites and services, or otherwise display third-party content. We do this for your convenience. We don't control and aren't responsible for their Web practices. Whether their content appears within our Web environment, or you leave our Web site for another site to view it, the terms, conditions, and privacy policies of those third-party sites govern your online experience (unless we have also linked our privacy policy and/or terms and conditions to some portion of the third-party site). Please view their terms of service and privacy policies if you have any question about their practices.

Here's a partial list of the sites or content of these third parties: 1\. Inline Framing We may provide content on our Web site that exists on other Web sites, such as live or recorded video, through a frame surrounded by content from our Web site (this framed content is referred to as an iFrame). The iFrame is used to facilitate easy access to the content from the other Web site.

     2. Sweepstakes, Contests, and Survey Sites

We may rely on the expertise of third-party service providers to run sweepstakes, contests, and surveys. Navigation to these sites may be seamless so that it appears you're still in our Web site environment. In these cases, the third-party's privacy policy may apply to any personal information you provide in connection with the event. So please take note of who's running the event in question and the terms, conditions, and policies that apply.

     3. Social Networking or Other User-Generated-Content Sites, and Other Websites

We may at times facilitate easy access to third-party sites, like social networking sites and other sites that host user-generated content. This may include easy click-through access or even "single-sign on" to these sites. The privacy policies of these third parties apply to the information collected by the third parties at these sites.

Our privacy policy, too, will apply at these sites if we display our content and feature our privacy policy there--but only to the extent that you directly provide us with your personal information, or we collect or observe this information through technology (as described above in Information We Observe or Collect through Technology). In these cases, we may display or link our privacy policy and terms and conditions. For example, you may find a third-party social media site (e.g., Facebook) where you can interact with us through a frame, e.g., you may virtually enter the frame to buy Luxola products. In this example, our displayed or linked privacy policy would apply to activities within that frame; however, the third-party's privacy policy would apply otherwise. Check all applicable policies when visiting such sites.

Note too, the social media sites where Luxola has a social media page may provide aggregate information and analysis to us about visitors' use of these social media pages. The analysis that is provided allows us to better understand and analyze our user growth, general demographic information about the users of our social media pages and interaction with content on our social media pages.

     4. Third-Party Rewards or Membership Programs

We may interact with certain unrelated companies that offer their customers memberships to participate in programs, which may include rewards for purchases from us. If you become a member of one of these programs or purchase something from us at this Web site through such a program, we may provide the company administering the membership program enough information about you or your purchase (like contact information, transaction date, transaction amount, and order number) to enable it to honor your membership.

We are not responsible for the privacy practices of the companies sponsoring these membership programs. Their terms, conditions, and policies apply to any information that's provided to them to further their programs.

**What information do we share with partners and third parties (or what information may they access because of the services they provide to us)?**

We may share information about you with partners and third parties, as described below, and as otherwise described in this policy: 1\. Select Brands We may also share the information described in this policy, like mailing and email address, customer preferences, and purchase history with select brands or partners such as Estee Lauder if you specifically purchase their products so that they market other products and services that may be of interest to you.

     2. Contractors

We use third-party "back-office" contractors to help handle parts of our business because of their expertise, resources, or scale. They help us do things like fulfill orders, process payments, monitor and analyze site activity, maintain databases, administer and monitor emails, administer and send mobile messages, serve ads on this and other Web sites as described above, and provide consulting services. Contractors may also assist us in hosting microsites, our mobile web sites and social media pages where you may provide personal information about you and others you know; and where they may observe information about you in the same way as described above (see What Personal Information Is Collected At Our Web Site or Online Channel Where this Policy is Displayed or Linked, and How Is It Used?).

     3. Other Marketers

We may share your name, postal address, and summary purchase information with other merchants and merchant exchanges. Other merchants may, in turn, use this information to send you offers on their products and services.

     4. Law Enforcement and Emergency Response

We may disclose specific information about our Web-site visitors if we have a good-faith belief that it's necessary or authorized under the law to protect our customers, the public, or our business.

     5. Sale, Acquisition, Merger or other Reorganization

In the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business assets, or acquire another business entity or are involved in a corporate reorganization or other change of control, consumer information may be shared and may be one of the business assets that is transferred as part of the transaction.

**What choices do you have over how your information is used?**

     1. Email

If at any time you'd like to stop future delivery of our email offers, simply follow the removal instructions located at the bottom of each message. This will stop future email offers from us, but won't stop operational or transactional messages such as email confirmations of your online orders or Customer Care communications. You may also call us at +65 8493 7315. We may occasionally provide you with the opportunity to opt in to receive email messages from third parties. If you do opt in, we'll share your email address with the specific third party with which you have opted in. Please review their privacy policies to see how they treat your personal information.

     2. Mobile Messaging

If you've signed up for recurring mobile messaging (e.g., SMS and MMS) offers but later decide you no longer wish to receive them, simply follow the applicable opt-out instructions, which are usually included in the mobile message itself. You may also call us at +65 8493 7315.

     3. Postal Mailers

If you'd like to specify your preferences for offers by postal mail, simply follow the instructions on each catalog, or call us at +65 8493 7315.

     4. Cookies, Clear Gifs, and Online Network Advertising

You may always choose to block cookies or even clear cookies from your computer. Simply follow your browser's instructions on how to block and clear cookies. Note that blocking cookies may not block the "first-party" cookies that are placed on your computer when you visit this site. By first-party cookies, we mean those cookies (whether placed by us or a contractor) that help us see how visitors use our site. Otherwise clearing cookies after each visit here will prevent observations from multiple sessions being aggregated over time. Please consider the consequences of blocking or clearing cookies. Many Web sites rely on their cookies to provide you with services or features that you have requested or expect.

     5. Other Marketers

If you don't want your basic contact and purchase information shared with other marketers (other than our affiliates and our contractor/service providers), please click here.

**How do you update your personal information?**

We prefer to keep your personal information accurate and up-to-date. You may update or modify your billing- and shipping- related information, and other account information, by logging onto our sites or calling us at +65 8493 7315.

**How do we secure your information on our site?**

Our Web site has the following types of security measures: limited access data-centers, firewall technology, and (for our e-Commerce sites through which you may place orders) secure-socket-layer (SSL) certificate authentication and payment tokenization. SSL is encryption technology that provides security for information that's transmitted over the Internet. Payment tokenization is the replacement of sensitive credit card data with a unique identifier that cannot be mathematically reversed. In our environment, tokens take the place of sensitive credit card data. While we implement the above security measures on our site, you should be aware that 100% security is not always possible.

**Where is personal information stored and processed?**

All our online channels are based in the U.S. where we store and process personal information. This privacy policy governs the information collected at this site or the online channel where the policy is displayed or linked, irrespective of where you're located when you access it, browse it, interact with it, and make purchases through it. This means your personal information may be stored outside of the province, state, and/or country in which you reside, and processed by us, an affiliate or a third-party service provider as described in this privacy policy.

**How do we address children’s privacy?**

We do not knowingly collect or maintain information provided by children under the age of 13.

**Whom should you contact with questions or concerns?**

If you have questions or concerns with respect to our Privacy Policy, please feel free to email us at contact@luxola.com or call us at +65 8493 7315.

This Privacy Statement is effective November 14, 2014.
